I said if you won't save me
http://animetranscripts.wikispaces.com
It's all that I've ever known...
Callin' out to all
If you know what I mean...
It's all that I've ever known
Please don't waste my time
Here am I, lost and found...
A dying scream makes no sound
Callin' out to all that I've ever known
Calling him up in-and-out of nowhere
We live a dying dream...
I tried to talk with God to no avail
Catch the wheel that breaks a butterfly
Cry the rain that fills the ocean wide
Attention all passengers, the plane is about to land.
皆様、当機は着陸態勢に入りました。
Please make sure that you've fastened your seatbelts.
シートベルトを緩みの無い様、しっかりお締めください。
Did I wake you up?
起こしちゃった？ おはよう。
小さなお子様をお連れのお客様は…
Good morning.
Hey, is that the site of the missile attack we saw on the news in Washington?
ねえ、あれってワシントンのニュースで見た
ミサイル攻撃の跡だよね？
そうみたいだね…
Seems so.
But there appear to be other spots that look similar. Were those caused by missile attacks as well?
でさ、他にも同じ様なのがあるんだけど
あれもミサイルの跡かな？
They are.
そうだよ。
マジ？
Really?!
However, the Hole over there is probably left behind from the 'Careless Monday' incident.
でも、あっちのは『迂闊な月曜日』の時にできた穴だよ、多分。
Careless Monday?
『迂闊な…月曜日』？
That's right... Today's a Monday as well...
そういえば今日、月曜日だ…
Episode 2
Melancholy Monday
They're all from Oosugi-kun...
全部、大杉くん…
内定者面談、やっぱり間に合わなかったな。
Looks like I won't make it in time for the interview.
The missile downed a plane, too.
ミサイルで飛行機も墜落だって。
A boy and girl were saved
Relay
11th missile!
六歳の男の子と女の子が一人ずつ
奇跡的に助かったみたいだけど。
A boy and girl, both 6 years old,
managed to miraculously survive.
Survivors in the wreckage
うそ！？ ミサイルで人が死んだの！？
Impossible! People died in the missile attack?!
There weren't any casualties during the previous incidents.
前は一人も犠牲者は出なかったじゃない。
I see.  That's why it's so crowded...
そっか、だからこんなに…
What do you mean?
どういうこと？ 犠牲者はでなかったって…
There weren't any casualties?
『迂闊な月曜日』は誰も死ななかったでしょう？
No one died during the Careless Monday incident, right?
なんで！？
Why?
なんでって…
Even if you ask me why...
Incoming Caller
Ohsugi
もしもし…
Hello?
や！咲ちゃん？ よかったあ！ もう空港なの？
Ah, Saki-chan?
Thank goodness. Have you reached the airport?
Looks like the plane landed on time.
定刻通りに着いたらしいな。
こっちは全然無事。
We're doing fine here.
Your sister's place wasn't affected at all.
お姉さんのところもまったく被害は無いよ。
Yeah.
Saki-chan, your interview's today, right?
咲ちゃん今日、内定者面談でしょ？
We're coming in a car to pick you up now.
今、車で迎えに行ってるから。
Yeah, that's right.
そう。
Oosugi, you make it sound easy,
but we probably won't make it there on time.
大杉い、軽く言ってるけど、こっちが間に合いそうも無いぞ。
いや、大丈夫だから待ってて！ 必ず間に合うように…！
No, we'll be okay. Just wait for us.
We'll definitely make—
あ！咲ちゃん！？
Saki-chan?
切れちゃった…
I got cut off.
ミサイルの影響かなあ？
Could this be caused by the missiles?
違うと思う。
I don't think so.
何なんだよぉ？ 皆してェ…！
What's wrong with you guys?
お前等本当仲良いよな。
You guys really get along so well with each other.
Didn't you just come back together
two days ago from your trip to America?
一昨日一緒にアメリカ旅行から帰ってきたばっかりだろうが。
Come to think of it, there isn't room for Saki-chan in here!
ていうか、これじゃあ咲ちゃんの乗るところが無いでしょおお！！
Your boyfriend?
彼氏？
N-No.
あっ、ううん。
Takizawa-kun, your phone's ringing.
滝沢君こそ電話！
もしもし？
Hello?
ジュイスです。
This is Juiz.
君かあ。
So it's you...
ナンバー９、セレゾンシステムの有効圏内に入りました。
Number 9, you are now within
effective range of the Selecao System.
Please carry out your duty as an elite immediately.
ただちに持てる者の義務を遂行してください。
My 'duty as an elite'?
持てる者の義務？
ね、ね、ちょっと、ジュイス！
Hey, Juiz, wait a minute!
Juiz?
ジュイス？
あ、もしもし、私、森見と申しますが、
Ah, hello?
I'm Morimi.
Is Yamada-san from HR around?
人事部の山田さんをお願いいたします。
君の言ってる事、全然分かんないんだけどさあ。
I don't understand what's going on.
俺が何で自分の記憶を消したか知ってたら教えてよ。
You know why I erased my memories, don't you?
Tell me why!
さあ～？ 私は記憶を消す方法をご紹介しただけ。
Who knows? I only showed you how to do it.
Feel free to ask me to do anything you wish.
今後もご要望がございましたら、何なりとお申し付けください。
The amount of money remaining for our services is ¥8,262,307,719.
ご奉仕可能な残りの金額は、
八十二億六千二百三十万七千七百十九円となっております。
8.2 billion?!
八十二億？
あなたにはそれを全額使い切る義務がございます。
You need to use up all of that money.
'Need'? It's not a privilege?
義務？ 権利じゃなくて？
はい。私はあなたのコンシェルジュ。
Indeed. I'm your concierge.
今後も最大限の手助けをしてまいります。
I'll continue to do my best to help you.
よく分かんないけど、
I don't really understand, but does this mean that you'll do anything to fulfill my wishes?
君は俺の言うことを何でも叶えてくれるってこと？
That's basically the gist of it.
ありていにいえば、そういうことです。
んじゃあさ、今空港にいるんだけど、
In that case, I'm currently at the airport.
ここから早く出たいんだ。
I want to get out of here quickly.
どう？できるかな？
So, can you do that?
Request accepted. Noblesse Oblige.
受理されました。
ノブレスオブリージュ。 今後も救世主足らんことを。
Please continue your work as a Savior.
Am I Number 9?
九番って俺か？
I'm sorry about this!
申し訳ございません。道を、お分けください！
Please make way!
W-What's going on?
な…なに…？
ニート大量失踪事件に関係していると思われる、
We've discovered a twenty-four year old unemployed man who might be connected to all those missing NEETs.
二十四歳無職の男性の事情聴取に向かってください。
Please head out and investigate.
引き篭りが大量に家出たんなら、いいことじゃねえか。
Isn't it a good thing that so many shut-ins actually stepped outside their houses?
What's up this time?
今度は何だ？
Golfing entertainment expenses for
a member of the Immigration Bureau
- Airport escape     [Details]
Balance:
Selecao Activity Log
Updates
History
Delete
九番？なんだこりゃ？
Number 9?
What the heck is this?
あからさまの賄賂じゃねえか。
Isn't this obviously bribery?
Balance:
A pack of plum-flavored gum at Tokyo Intl. Airport
しかも梅ガムって。
And he bought plum flavored gum too... How careless.
迂闊してんなあ
待てよ…
Wait a minute...
All kinds of gum
Place your card here
Thank you.
ありがとうございました。
へえー、こんな使い方もできるんだー。
So it can be used like this, too?
Airport Escape
[Details]
Balance:
Seleção Activity Log
Updates
History
Delete
A pack of plum-flavored
gum at Tokyo Intl. Airport
Balance:
Airport Escape
It's someone famous!
芸能人だよ！
Thank you!
やあ！どうもー！
あの、チョーハズカシイんですけど…
Um... This is quite embarrassing...
誰かと間違えられてんのかな？
Could it be that they've mistaken us for someone else?
それとも滝沢君、実はセレブ？
Or are you really a celebrity, Takizawa-kun?!
どうかなー？
Who knows...
Hey, Takizawa-kun,
ね、滝沢君。
do you have any plans for later?
この後、何か予定とかある？
Nope.
いやー。
実は今日の予定とか全部狂っちゃって、
この後フリーなんだけど、
Actually, my plans for today are all messed up.
I'm free after this...
Would you mind if we had tea together or something?
よかったら少しお茶でもしてかない？
Well, it might sound weird,
あのさあ、変なこと言って悪いんだけど、
実は俺、自分が誰なのか全然分かんないんだ。
but I don't remember anything about myself.
I don't have any memories of what I was doing before you met me at the White House.
ホワイトハウスより前の記憶が無くってさ…
I can't remember my name,
or what I was doing before that.
名前とか今まで何やってたのかとかは
まったく思い出せないんだ。
で、まずは自分が誰なのか突き止めなきゃならないから、
So, I have to find out who I am first.
とりあえず、パスポートの住所に行ってみようと思うんだ。
For now, I'll take a look at the address in my passport.
だから…ここで別れよう。
So let's split up here.
じゃ！
See ya!
うそお…
No way...
たしか九番は今まで死んでたはずだがなあ…
Number 9 should be dead.
Could it be that someone else picked it up?
もしかしてこいつを誰かに拾われたとか…
No one other than me would use it like that.
でなきゃ、こんな使い方しねえだろ…俺以外。
What's going on?
なんなのお？ 結構仲良くなれたと思ってたのにィ！
I thought that we'd become pretty good friends...
ヒドイ顔…
I look awful.
Could it be that I'm not smiling enough?
笑顔が足りなかったかなあ…？
十分いい笑顔だった！
Your smile's very pretty!
や。
What are you doing?!
何やってんの！？
This is basically illegal!
ギリ犯罪だし！
Um... Where is Toyosu?
あのさあ、豊洲ってどこだっけ？
今度は堂々とモノレールに乗りやがった…
Now he's openly taking a ride on the monorail.
I thought he was just messing around, but...
ちょっと面だけでもと思ったんだが…
What's wrong?
どーした？
This address is close to the Hole.
この住所、穴のすぐ近くだよ。
The place where the missiles were dropped on Careless Monday.
『迂闊な月曜日』にミサイルが落ちたとこ…
Third Northern Elementary
Toyosu Preschool
Home Center
Toyosu branch
Shopping Center
Chida General
Toyosu
Toyosu Station
Museum
of Science
Danger
Entry Forbidden
Toyosu Park
Toyosu Tower
このへんって今は廃墟になってるはずだけど…
The area around it is pretty much in ruins now.
じゃあ、俺の家も無くなってるかなあ？
So, my house is gone too?
Yeah...
Hey, just how many of those 'Holes' are there?
ねえ、その穴ってさあ、一体いくつあるの？
そもそもなんでミサイル攻撃があったの？
Why were they attacked with missiles in the first place?
Including yesterday's one, there are eleven in total.
昨日のを入れたら全部で十一個かな？
理由は分からないけど、
去年の十一月二十二日の月曜日に突然飛んできたの。
We still don't know why, but the missiles were launched suddenly on Monday, the 22nd of November, last year.
自衛隊も警察も政治家も
Neither the SDF, the police, nor the politicians
ever imagined that Japan would be struck by missiles.
日本がミサイル攻撃されるなんて夢にも思ってなくて…
それで首相が臨時ニュースで迂闊だったって言っちゃったの。
Because of that, the Prime Minister said,
"We were too careless" during the special news bulletin.
So that's why it was called Careless Monday.
それで『迂闊な月曜日』…
そう。で、後になって一人も犠牲者が
出ていなかったことが分かって…
Yup. We found out later that there weren't any casualties.
The Internet and the media were awash with speculation over who was responsible.
ネットもマスコミも、犯人探しのお祭り騒ぎになっちゃったの。
Some said that it was an attack by our neighboring countries,
隣国の攻撃だとか、アメリカの陰謀だとか、
some that it was an American conspiracy,
and others said that it was government subterfuge...
政府の自作自演だとか…
However, it just felt too perfect to be real, so nobody felt alarmed in any way.
でも、確かにあんまりにも出来過ぎた感じだったから、
皆どこか、危機感なくなっちゃって…
不謹慎だけど少しワクワクしてて、
It's pretty stupid, but I can't help getting a little excited when I think of what other amazing things could happen.
もっと何か凄いことが起こらないかなって思ってた。
Number 9, where are you?
どこだ？九番。
Updates
History
Delete
Switch
Display
Function
Exiting the monorail at Tennozu Isle
Boarding the monorail at Haneda
A pack of plum-flavored gum at
Tokyo Intl. Airport
He's nearby.
当りだ、ちきしょう、まだこの中に…
Dammit, he should still be here...
だめかあ…
This is hopeless.
Hey, old man!
おっさん！
You've got the same cellphone as me.
御揃いっすね、その携帯。
おっさんももしかして記憶無いんですか？
Old man, could it be that you've lost your memories too?
ああ？何言ってる？
Huh? What do you mean?
Oh. It's nothing. Sorry.
いや、何でもないんです！
すみません、ちょっと気になったもんで。
I was just curious.
そいじゃ！
Bye!
おおい、ちょっと待て、兄ちゃん。
お前、セレソンか？
Wait up, lad.
Are you a Selecao?
Selecao?
セレソン？
俺ぁ警察だ。
I'm a police officer.
最近何かと物騒なんでな…
It's been dangerous around here lately.
一応身分を確認させてもらうぞ。
Let me check your ID.
ID?
身分ですか…
Takizawa Akira, and you live in Toyosu.
滝沢朗。
住所は豊洲。
そうか。
Okay then.
次はわけ分かんねえこと言ってるとしょっぴくからな！
Be careful, you might just get arrested if you talk nonsense like that again.
気をつけます。
I'll be careful.
じゃあ、刑事さん、また！
Bye then, Mr. Police Officer.
あいつが九番のセレソンか…
He's the ninth Selecao?
How useless.
ヘタ売ったな。
船が着たらもういいよ。
You can leave once the boat arrives.
I can go on alone from here.
ここからは一人で行けそうだから。
Here's your coffee and the remaining 760 yen.
はい、コーヒー。
と、お釣り七百六十円。
ありがとう。
Thanks. You can keep the change.
お釣りはいいよ。
You don't have any cash on you, right?
現金持ってないんでしょ？
True. Thanks, then.
じゃあ、ありがたく。
It'd be great if your house is still there.
滝沢君家、残ってるといいね。
んまあ、無かったら無かったで、何か考えるよ。
If it's gone, it's gone. I'll think of something.
そうだ、俺は空っぽだからさ、代わりに君の事教えてよ。
Oh yeah, since I have no memories, why don't you talk about yourself?
私のこと？
Me?
Just tell me whatever you can about yourself before the boat arrives.
うん。
船が着いちゃうまでの間…可能な限り。
U-Um... I'm in my fourth year of university, and I'll be working in April...
えっと、私は大学四年生で、四月から就職が決まってて…
Working? Where?
就職するんだ。
どこ？
At a firm my brother-in-law used to work at.
お姉ちゃんの旦那様の元いた会社。
お姉ちゃんいるんだ。
You've got a sister?
Yeah... Um...
あの、変に気ィ使わないで欲しいんだけど、
I hope you don't think I'm weird, but both my parents are dead.
私…両親いないんだ…
事故だったの。
They died in an accident.
その時、お姉ちゃんはもう結婚してて…
My sister was already married then.
私は受験止めて働こうって思ったんだけど、
I was thinking about skipping my exams and starting work,
旦那さんと二人で家の仕事継いでくれて…
but the two of them took over our family business and allowed me to attend university.
大学行かせてくれたの。
You have a kind sister.
いいお姉さんだね。
Yeah, Ryousuke-san is kind t—
Oh, that's my brother-in-law.
うん。
良介さんも…お姉ちゃんの旦那さんね！
My sister gave birth to a baby last year, and the four of us live together.
で、去年生まれたお姉ちゃんの赤ちゃんと、四人で暮らしてる。
良介さんは、どんな人？
What's Ryousuke-san like?
そんな急かさないで！
Don't rush me!
Ryousuke-san is very sincere.
良介さんは、とっても誠実な人。
お姉ちゃんが大学の時から付き合ってて、
He dated my sister when they were in university.
They decided to get married the moment they met each other.
はじめて会ったときから二人は結婚するなあって…
かっこいいんだ。
Is he cool?
まあね。お姉ちゃんにしてはいい趣味してる。
I guess. My sister has pretty good taste.
That's good. Feels like a family.
いいね、家族って感じだ。
It's not all good, though.
でも、いいことばっかりじゃないよ。
I feel ashamed, since I always depend on them.
世話になりっぱなしで、肩身が狭い。
そっか。
I see...
Somehow I've remembered something after hearing your story.
君の話を聞いててさ、
俺なんか一個だけ記憶が蘇ったみたい。
本当？
Really?
When I was around five years old, someone gave me 500 yen when I was at a department store.
五歳くらいのとき、デパートで誰かに五百円もらったんだ。
これで何でも好きなもの買って来なさいって。
They told me, "Go and buy whatever you want with this."
I was wondering if I should go by myself, and they told me,
で、俺が一人で行くのを躊躇ってたら、その人が、
"Don't worry. Adults and children are treated the same as long as they have money."
大丈夫。金さえあれば大人も子供も同じだからって言ったんだ。
そのとき何を買ったかは忘れちゃったけど、
I've forgotten what I bought then,
but I remember that the old guy at the counter bowed deeply to me when I paid him the money.
レジで金払ったら、
そのおっさんが深々と俺に頭下げたのはっきり覚えてる。
I was really happy and said,
"It's just like Mom told me!" as I turned back...
それで俺、嬉しくなって、
ほんとだ母さんの言うとおりだって言って振り返って…
This is a memory of my mother!
あっ、これ、お袋の記憶だ！
でも、振り返ったら、その人の姿は消えてて…
However, I lose sight of her when I turn back...
その後、二度と会ったことはないと思う…
I haven't seen her since then.
So sad...
そんな…
At least I remembered that I had a mother.
でも、お袋のいたことは思い出せた。
Farewell.
それじゃ。
Wait, we haven't even exchanged e-mail addresses yet...
行かないで…まだメルアドも交換してないよ…
おやじ、一杯頼む。
Mister, a drink please.
The monorail, plum flavored gum,
and bribing the immigration office...
モノレール、梅ガム、入管での賄賂。
Updates
History
Delete
A pack of plum-flavored gum at
Tokyo Intl. Airport
Balance:
Airport Escape: Golfing
entertainment expense...
[Details]
Balance:
Memory wipe program download from
ATO Harima Neuro Science
Updates
History
Delete
A pack of plum-flavored gum at
Tokyo Intl. Airport
Balance:
Airport Escape: Golfing
entertainment expense...
[Details]
Balance:
Memory wipe program download from
ATO Harima Neuro Science
Balance:
A brainwashing program at Harima Encephalological Laboratory...
播磨脳科学研究所の洗脳プログラム…
I don't know why, but he tampered with his own memories.
あいつ、理由は分かんねえが自分で記憶をどうかしたんだ。
Purchase a theater
Balance:
Two weeks of convenience store
meal delivery for 20k people
Balance:
Purchase an urban shopping mall
Updates
History
Delete
Balance:
Two weeks of convenience store
meal delivery for 20k people
Balance:
Purchase an urban shopping mall
He even bought out a shopping mall in Toyosu.
さらに豊洲のショッピングモール。
How are these going to contribute to this country?
しかし、これのどこがこの国に貢献してるんだ？
He's lousier than me if you look at it from a certain perspective.
あいつ、ある意味俺以下かもしれねえぞお？
ご機嫌ですねえ。
You seem to be in a good mood.
俺に二度目の強運が回ってきたみたいだからさ。
It seems that fortune is going to favor me for the second time.
それはよかった近藤さん。
Isn't that wonderful, Kondou-san?
だったら二千万、直ぐに返してくださいよ？
Hurry up and return the ¥20,000,000 you owe us.
We'll let it slide if you provide us with the police's internal list of people with many debts...
うちとしては、
警察内部の多重債務者リストでも構わないんですけどねえ？
うん。うん。空港でずっと足止めされちゃって…
I was delayed at the airport for a long time.
うん。そのことは明日説明するから…
I'll explain it to you tomorrow.
今日はみっちょんところに泊まる。
I'll stay at Micchan's place for today.
うん。ごめんね。
Sorry.
ねえ！ニューヨーク行ったって言ってたよね！
Hey, you said that you went to New York, right?
Did you go to Fifth Avenue?
じゃあさ五番街とか行った？
行ったよ！ティファニー！
I went to Tiffany's.
何も買わなかったけど…
I didn't buy anything, though.
I took this in Times Square.
これ…タイムズスクエア。
I went to see The Lion King in the evening.
夜、ライオンキングを見に行ったの。
Oh?
Where else did you go?
他にはどんなとこ行った？
I went to Central Park, saw the Statue of Liberty, and walked along the Brooklyn Bridge.
セントラルパーク行って、自由の女神見て、
ブルックリンブリッジを歩いて…
That gothic-style bridge?
あのゴシック調の橋？
Yup! You sure know a lot!
そ！よく知ってるね！
映画で見ただけだけど。
I only saw it in a movie, though.
The bridge was used as a time-travel tunnel in one of Meg Ryan's movies, right?
メグライアンの映画で
この橋、タイムトンネルになってたでしょ？
I don't know. I don't watch movies that much.
知らない。
あんまり、映画見ないから…
そう。
Oh... I thought girls loved to watch movies.
女の子なら見てると思ったんだけど…
ちぇ、映画の記憶はやけに鮮明なんだけどなあ。
Hmph, my memories of movies are still so vivid.
他にどんなの覚えてる？
Do you remember anything else?
記憶が戻る手がかりになるかも…
We might be able to find some clues about how to get your memories back.
一番好きな映画は何？
What's your favorite movie?
Who knows? I've pretty much forgotten everything about myself.
さあーて。
そもそも自分のことはほとんど忘れてるからなあ…
I see...
そっかあ。
Hey, where's this one?
ねえ、これは？
That's the Freedom Tower.
それは、フリーダムタワー。
Freedom Tower?
フリーダムタワー…
グラウンドゼロの跡地に新しく建ったビル。
It's a new building that was constructed on the site of Ground Zero.
9/11の
9/11?
これはまだ、映画になってないな、多分。
That probably hasn't made it into a movie yet.
It's strange, but the level ground is very beautiful.
不思議だったよー。
何かペロンと奇麗で
I've always wanted to visit Ground Zero.
グラウンド・ゼロは一度行ってみたかったんだけど、
もう十年前の面影は全然無かった。
It's already completely different from how it was ten years ago.
Even so, I feel that we should never forget that incident.
でも、なんかアノ事件のこと忘れちゃいけない様な気がする。
ちょっといい？
Just a second.
What do you think?
どう？
グラウンドゼロ
Ground Zero.
Can you send me this photo?
この写真、もらってもいい？
ああ。
Sure.
やり方分かんねえや
I don't know how to work this, you do it.
やって！
近藤さん、今後もこの状態が続くようだと…
Kondou-san, if you continue to refuse to pay up,
we might have to reluctantly  drop by your workplace for a visit.
不本意ながら職場をお尋ねすることになりますが…
As if I care.
知るか。
ジュイス、この二人を殺せ。
Juiz, kill these two.
受理しました。
Request accepted. Noblesse Oblige.
ノブレスオブリージュ。
Please continue your work as a Savior.
今後も救世主足らんことを。
How annoying.
うるせえ。
What are you up to?
何のまねだ？
人生をやり直すのさ。
I'm restarting my life.
追い詰められておかしくなったかあ？
Have we driven him mad by chasing him?
Bang!
バーン。
Juiz, him too.
ジュイス、あいつもだ。
悪いな。
Sorry.
Bang!
バーン。
The way things are now,
a lone detective isn't enough to enforce justice.
今時、刑事が一人足掻いたって、正義はなせねえんだよ。
Entertainment
Electronic scoreboard manipulation
Tokyo Racecourse - Race #7 - Lots of
trifecta boxes
Selecao Activity Log
Updates
History
Delete
Switch
Display
Function
Balance:
Kill these 3 in
front of me
[Details]
Entertainment
Electronic scoreboard manipulation
まあ、いいや、待ってろ九番。
Oh well.
Wait for me, Number 9.
お前の義務を俺が貰ってやるからよ。
I'll take over your duty.
夜は封印
戸惑い混じれば終わる
迷い出すぐらいならいっそ
わ     け
理由も捨てよう
また夢に溺れる
不確かに続いてく未来
まだ君を許せる
意味を知れる
耳を澄ますための夜
その理由を真似て変われる
君の呼吸を知るために
未来の根を切っても構わない